<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AstaGuru</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="terms_conditons">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>

    <string name="action_refresh">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_new">Settings</string>
    <string name="logo_desc">App logo</string>
    <string name="country_name">Nigeria</string>
    <string name="terms_condition">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>

    <string name="selectsource">Select a source</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="doller">$</string>
    <string name="rupees">₹</string>
    <string name="data">AstaGuru was conceptualised in the year 2008, with the sole purpose of creating a safe and secure platform to conduct online auctions for Contemporary &amp; Modern Indian Art, however we are constantly innovating &amp;
    venturing into exciting new spectrums such as vintage collectibles and rear antiques, which include fine writing instruments, timepieces, celebrity memorabilia &amp;
    aristocratic jewelry. The word AstaGuru is a combination of Asta which means auction in Italian and Guru which
    indicates our mastery at conducting the same. With the world becoming whole on a digital level, we are able to showcase Indian Art &amp; Antiques with a prevalent legacy, on a global scale. Successfully linking the perspective buyer and consignor without any geographic constraints. With AstaGuru it is now possible for Art collectors and admirers to par take and get their fill of the exploding Indian Art culture. Our stringent selection process
    ensures only prime artworks &amp; exquisite antiques are part of our auctions. Numerous criteria such as the
    provenance of the work, the rarity of the work, and its physical condition are assessed before their inclusion in our auctions.\n\nUnder the leadership of Mr Vickram Sethi, founder &amp;
    chairman of The Arts Trust, Institute of Contemporary Indian Art Gallery, Mumbai &amp; AstaGuru and Mr Tushar Sethi, CEO AstaGuru, we are treading towards a horizon filled with Art, Antiques &amp; Bliss.\n\nTheir keen eye and impeccable knowledge leverages us with insights of current &amp; future trends. Our aim is to manifest Indian Art globally and create a conducive
    environment that spurts it\s growth and to constantly
    reinvent ourselves in order to cater to the needs of our esteemed clientele.</string>
    <string name="html"><![CDATA[

                             <div class="ui-accordion-content ui-helper-reset ui-widget-content ui-corner-bottom" id="ui-id-8" aria-labelledby="ui-id-7" role="tabpanel" aria-hidden="true" style="display: none; font-family:WorkSans; font-size:85%; text-align:justify; color:#606060;">

                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Pre -Registration and Verification.</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy bidding_list">
                                <li style="text-align: justify!important;">Prospective buyers should be registered and verified in order to bid.</li>
                                <li>If you have already registered before, you will still need to pre-register and accept the terms and conditions for the sale. (Use your previous login Id).</li>
                                <li>Fill the form online in order to pre-register, or call AstaGuru.</li>
                                <li>Once you have pre-registered a representative will call you to verify your details.</li>
                                <li>If the representative cannot reach you an email will be sent.</li>
                                <li>Please note that if this process has not taken place you shall not be given bidding access.</li>
                                <li>All bidding access shall be provided 24 hours before the auction.</li>
                                <li>Once your application has been accepted you shall receive an email confirming your bidding access along with your Login Id and password.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Absentee Bids</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>You may place an absentee bid, by faxing the written bid form available online and in the printed catalogue.</li>
                                <li>All bids must come in 24 hours before the auction.</li>
                            </ul>

							<div class="buytitle"><strong>Proxy Bids</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                  <li>Proxy bids shall be placed on the website once the auction catalogue goes live and will be available until the end of the auction. </li>
		 <li>Once you have identified the lot that you would like to bid on, click on "Proxy bid" and enter desired amount(10% more than the previous bid) and confirm your bid at the value submitted.</li>
			<li>In case of the "No Reserve" auction all proxy bid values start at Rs 20,000.</li>
        <li>Proxy bid placed on a lot before an auction cannot be resubmitted online. Users can update such proxy bids by submitting a duly signed written bid form provided on the website.</li>

								<li>In case a user is outbid on their proxy, they will be intimated of the same and can update the proxy online if they wish to so.</li>
								<li>Astaguru reserves the right to reject any proxy bid at its discretion without having to provide any explaination.</li>
                            </ul>


                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Opening Bid</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Opening Bid is the value at which the auction house starts the bidding of each lot.</li>
                                <li>Opening bid is 20% lower than value of the lower estimate.</li>
                                <li>In case of the "No Reserve" auction all bids start at Rs 20,000.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Bidding Online</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Once you have identified the lot that you would like to bid on, click on "Bid Now" confirm your bid at the value listed</li>
                                <li>This is where you participate in the bidding process, by entering the next valid bid each time you are out-bid.</li>
                                <li>The next valid bid will be a 10% increment in value of the last valid bid.</li>
                                <li>All lots bid history will be made available to be viewed.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Bid Increments</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>All bids will have an increment of 10% of the current valid bid</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Personalized Bid Notifications</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>In case you&ampre outbid on a particular lot you will be notified of the same on your registered email and mobile number.</li>
								<li>In case you&ampve won a particular lot in an auction you will be notified of the same on your registered email and mobile number.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Bid History</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Bid history indicates the value recorded for each lot since the start of the auction</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Bid History will not be displayed once the auction has closed.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Currency of Bidding</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Bids can be placed in US Dollars (USD) or Indian Rupees (INR).</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Buyers in India must pay for their purchase in INR and all other buyers must pay in USD</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Closing and Winning Bid</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Winning bid is the last and highest bid at which the lot has closed.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>No new bids cannot be placed after the close of a lot.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>The closing bid is considered the winning bid only if the bid exceeds the reserve price.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>All winning bids shall be posted on the website after the close of the auction.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Bid Cancellation</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Once any bid and/or proxy bid has been placed, it cannot be cancelled. AstaGuru reserves the rights to cancel any bids in order to protect the efficacy of the bidding process.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <div class="buytitle"><strong>Buyers Premium</strong></div>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>In addition to the hammer price, the buyer agrees to pay to us the buyers premium calculated at 15% of the winning bid value on each lot.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <ul class="f14 c64 buy">
                                <li>Service tax on the buyers premium shall be applicable for paintings purchased within India.</li>
                            </ul>

                        </div>]]></string>
</resources>